[
    {
        "question": "â™–ğŸ”  ÙˆÙŠÙ„ÙŠØ§Ù…  ğŸ‘ŒğŸ˜º",
        "response": "ÙˆÙŠÙ„ÙŠØ§Ù…"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™•â˜  Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ  â™¢ğŸ­",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜¹ğŸ™  Ù„ÙˆÙÙŠ  ğŸ’›ğŸ‘»",
        "response": "Ù„ÙˆÙÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ©ğŸ‰  Ø§ÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ†  â™™âœŒ",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ†"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™£ğŸ‘‘  Ø§Ø³ØªØ§  â˜¯ğŸ©",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™ğŸ’š  Ù‡Ù…ØªØ§Ø±Ùˆ  ğŸ’˜ğŸ’¥",
        "response": "Ù‡Ù…ØªØ§Ø±Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŸğŸ’²  Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙŠÙÙŠØ§  ğŸ§ğŸ¯",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙŠÙÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜†ğŸ¯  Ù†ÙˆÙŠÙ„  â™¤â™š",
        "response": "Ù†ÙˆÙŠÙ„"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ…ğŸ¸  Ø±Ø§ÙŠÙ„ÙŠ  â™ŸğŸ‘",
        "response": "Ø±Ø§ÙŠÙ„ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ‹â™¬  Ø§Ù„  àµ âœ‹",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸğŸ’€  Ù„Ø§Ùˆ  â˜®â™”",
        "response": "Ù„Ø§Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’—ğŸ«  Ù…Ø§Ø¯Ø§Ø±Ø§  ğŸŸğŸ§",
        "response": "Ù…Ø§Ø¯Ø§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â–€â–„â–€â–„â–€â–„ ÙŠÙˆØ±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠ â–„â–€â–„â–€â–„â–€",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆØ±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™ğŸƒ  Ø§ÙŠØªØ§ØªØ´ÙŠ  â™âœŠ",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠØªØ§ØªØ´ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’£ğŸ‘Œ  ØªÙˆØ¨ÙŠ  â˜œğŸ ",
        "response": "ØªÙˆØ¨ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸğŸ†  Ù†ÙˆØ¨Ø§Ø±Ø§  ğŸ’”ğŸŸ",
        "response": "Ù†ÙˆØ¨Ø§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”  ğŸ€  Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ  ğŸ€  ğŸ”",
        "response": "Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜¢â›µ  Ù‡Ø§Ø´ÙŠØ±Ø§Ù…Ø§  â™ğŸ˜",
        "response": "Ù‡Ø§Ø´ÙŠØ±Ø§Ù…Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’ğŸ’™  Ø¨ÙˆØ±ÙˆØªÙˆ  ğŸ˜³â™•",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙˆØ±ÙˆØªÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’œğŸˆ  ÙŠÙˆØ³ÙˆØ¨  ğŸ’—ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆØ³ÙˆØ¨"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ°  ğŸ€  Ø±ÙŠÙ…  ğŸ€  ğŸ°",
        "response": "Ø±ÙŠÙ…"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜ ğŸ‘¤  Ø§ÙˆØªØ´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§ Ø´ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙŠ  â™¥â™ª",
        "response": "Ø§ÙˆØªØ´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§ Ø´ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ‹ğŸ”¥  ÙƒÙŠØ¯  ğŸˆâœ‹",
        "response": "ÙƒÙŠØ¯"
    },
    {
        "question": " â–‚ â–„ â–… â–† â–‡ â–ˆ Ù…ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø³Ø§ â–ˆ â–‡ â–† â–… â–„ â–‚",
        "response": "Ù…ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø³Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "(ã£â—”â—¡â—”)ã£ â™¥ Ø¯Ø§Ù†Ø²Ùˆ â™¥",
        "response": "Ø¯Ø§Ù†Ø²Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜®ğŸ’£  ÙˆÙŠÙ†Øº  àµ ğŸ˜",
        "response": "ÙˆÙŠÙ†Øº"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‰ğŸ˜º  ØªÙŠÙ†Ø´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§Ù†  ğŸ¼ğŸŠ",
        "response": "ØªÙŠÙ†Ø´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¨ÙŠÙƒÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙŠÙƒÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¥ğŸ‘‘  ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ  ğŸ‘®ğŸ’£",
        "response": "ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¤â™¤  Ø¬ÙŠØ±Ø§ÙŠØ§  ğŸ‘ºâ™¦",
        "response": "Ø¬ÙŠØ±Ø§ÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‰â˜¯  ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ  ğŸŠâ™•",
        "response": "ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™˜ğŸ‘¤  ÙƒÙˆÙƒÙˆÙ…ÙŠ  ğŸºğŸƒ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆÙƒÙˆÙ…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥ğŸ‘»  ØºÙŠÙˆ  â™¡ğŸ’š",
        "response": "ØºÙŠÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŸâ™¥  ØªØ´ÙŠÙˆ  ğŸŸâ˜¯",
        "response": "ØªØ´ÙŠÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥â™  Ø³Ø§Ø³ÙˆØ±ÙŠ  ğŸ‘£ğŸ‘¹",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ø³ÙˆØ±ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ·  ğŸ€  Ù†ÙŠØ²ÙˆÙƒÙˆ  ğŸ€  âœ·",
        "response": "Ù†ÙŠØ²ÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒ·ğŸ‰  Ù…ÙŠØ¯ÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§  ğŸ¸ğŸ‘½",
        "response": "Ù…ÙŠØ¯ÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™£âœŒ  Ù†ÙŠØ¬ÙŠ  ğŸºğŸ’",
        "response": "Ù†ÙŠØ¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸºğŸ¤  Ø§Ø³ØªØ§  ğŸ¯ğŸ¨",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‘ğŸ†  Ù„ÙŠØ²Ø§  â™¢ğŸ§",
        "response": "Ù„ÙŠØ²Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‘ğŸ¯  ÙƒØ§ØºÙˆÙŠØ§  ğŸ’€ğŸ£",
        "response": "ÙƒØ§ØºÙˆÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§  ğŸ€  Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§  ğŸ€  ğŸ§",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ“  ğŸ€  Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙƒØ§  ğŸ€  ğŸ“",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ä±llÄ±llÄ±   ğŸ€  Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ§  ğŸ€   Ä±llÄ±llÄ±",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤ğŸ¬  Ø²ÙŠÙ†ØªØ³Ùˆ  ğŸ’¢ğŸª",
        "response": "Ø²ÙŠÙ†ØªØ³Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘»ğŸ“  Ø±ÙŠÙ†ØºÙˆÙƒÙˆ  ğŸ§ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "Ø±ÙŠÙ†ØºÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’ğŸ’²  Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ  â˜†ğŸ’—",
        "response": "Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¢â˜Ÿ  ÙƒÙˆØ±ØªØ§  ğŸˆğŸ’£",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆØ±ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜ˆğŸˆ  Ù‡ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙƒØ§  ğŸ’™ğŸƒ",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ’â™˜  Ø§Ù†ÙˆØ³  ğŸ˜ğŸ‘‘",
        "response": "Ø§Ù†ÙˆØ³"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜ŸğŸˆ  Ø¨ÙŠØ§ÙƒÙˆØºØ§Ù†  ğŸ’â™§",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙŠØ§ÙƒÙˆØºØ§Ù†"
    },
    {
       "question": "ã€ï½¡_ï½¡ã€‘ Ø´ÙˆÙƒÙˆ ã€ï½¡_ï½¡ã€‘",
        "response": "Ø´ÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸğŸ§  Ø¯ÙŠÙƒÙˆ  ğŸ„âœŠ",
        "response": "Ø¯ÙŠÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "â–‘â–’â–“â–ˆ ÙŠØ§Ù…ÙŠ â–ˆâ–“â–’â–‘",
        "response": "ÙŠØ§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ†ğŸ‘  ÙØ§Ù†Ø¬Ø§Ù†Ø³  ğŸ®ğŸ…",
        "response": "ÙØ§Ù†Ø¬Ø§Ù†Ø³"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜®ğŸ¤  ÙŠÙˆÙ„ÙŠÙˆØ³  ğŸœâ™œ",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆÙ„ÙŠÙˆØ³"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ‘ŠâœŠ  ØªØ³ÙˆÙ…ÙˆØºÙˆ  ğŸ£ğŸ¨",
        "response": "ØªØ³ÙˆÙ…ÙˆØºÙˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ‘»ğŸ’›  Ù†Ø§Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ  ğŸƒğŸ’›",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ ğŸ  Ø§ÙŠØ²Ù†  â™—â™š",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠØ²Ù†"
    },
    {
       "question": "â™”ğŸ’  Ø²Ø§Ø±Ø§ÙƒÙŠ  âœŒâ˜†",
        "response": "Ø²Ø§Ø±Ø§ÙƒÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ»ğŸ’œ  Ø§ÙˆØ±Ø§Ù‡Ø§Ø±Ø§  â˜¹ğŸº",
        "response": "Ø§ÙˆØ±Ø§Ù‡Ø§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ©ğŸª  Ø§ÙŠÙ†ÙˆÙŠ  â˜¹ğŸ‘¹",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠÙ†ÙˆÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ‘½ğŸ‰  ØºÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†  ğŸ²â™",
        "response": "ØºÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ²â™•  ÙƒÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ„ÙŠÙ†  ğŸ˜²ğŸŠ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ„ÙŠÙ†"
    },
    {
       "question": "*â€¢.Â¸â™¡ Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ³ÙˆØ±Ùˆ â™¡Â¸.â€¢*",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ³ÙˆØ±Ùˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "-æ¼«~*'Â¨Â¯Â¨'*Â·èˆ~ Ø±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠÙ„ ~èˆ*'Â¨Â¯Â¨'*Â·~æ¼«-",
       "response": "Ø±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠÙ„"
}
]
